Just Add Romance is a tv movie, romance, comedy film directed by Terry Ingram.
When Carly and Jason, exact opposites, compete on a famed cooking show for the chance at their own
restaurant, what will matter more – their culinary careers or their potential love?
Carly, played by Meghann Fahy.
Jason, played by Luke Macfarlane.
Zoey, played by Brittney Wilson.
Tina, played by Debs Howard.
Lauren, played by Caitlin Stryker.
Female Student, played by Favour Onwuka.
It Was Just an Accident (Persian: یک تصادف ساده, romanized: Yek tasādof-e sāde; French: Un
simple accident) is a 2025 thriller film written and directed by Jafar Panahi.
The film is a co-production between Iran, France, and Luxembourg.
The film follows a group of former Iranian political prisoners who face the question of
whether to exact revenge on a man they believe may be their tormentor.
Panahi, who is critical of the Iranian government and has been imprisoned several times, made
the film without official filming permission from the Iranian authorities.
The film had its world premiere at the main competition of the 78th Cannes Film Festival on
20 May 2025, where it won the Palme d'Or, and received critical acclaim.
At the 83rd Golden Globe Awards, it became the first Iranian film to be nominated for Best Motion Picture –
Drama, Best Director and Best Screenplay, and was also nominated for Best Foreign Language Film.
At the 98th Academy Awards, it was nominated for Best International
Feature Film (France) and Best Original Screenplay.
It Was Just an Accident was theatrically released in France
on 1 October 2025 by Memento Distribution.
The film explores themes of cooking, food, culinary arts,
reality competition, food competition.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.